# **Tota Ali**

website developer

### Contact

- +880-1794964503
- totamotiuregmail.com
- Gurudaspur, Natore, Bangladesh
- https://totafreelancer.github.io/programmertota/

#### Skills

HTML

CSS

Tailwindcss

bootstrap

Javascript

React JS

SASS/SCSS

WordPress

PHP

Mysql

## Language

- English
- Bangla



## Profile

Hello there, I'm Tota Ali, a Web and WordPress developer, working as a WordPress, web developer and designer for several years in Redmo IT company. I am an expert in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React JS, Bootstrap, Tailwindcss, SASS/ACSS, WordPress, etc. Knowing your problems, I will be your best solution.

### Work Experience

Professional freelancer | Jan 2024 - Present

- Creating fonts and websites
- Image to HTML, PDF to HTML, Figma to HTML website creation
- Creating custom WordPress websites

FJunior frontend developer | Redmo IT | Jan 2022 - December 2023

- Creating fonts and websites
- Image to HTML, PDF to HTML, Figma to HTML website creation

## Education

- Muktijoddha Doctor Mohsin Ali College | 2020- 2022
- RDO Polytechnical Institute | Diploma in computer Engineering | 2022